We are here at Hotel Oyasato Izu, which was built by Tetsuya from Tokai On Air!
Glad to be here.
I see this place often.
Very nice!
You can cut like this.
There it is!
There's the orange one.
Good morning.
I'm Ayumi Ozawa from Mealy Caller.
I'm Mizuki Yoshida.
I'm Esmernon.
I'm Yuka Miyayama.
Pleased to meet you.
Let's get right to it. Where are you today?
Today, I'm at Hotel Ways, which was built by Mr. Tetsuya of Tokai On Air.
I'm here at Hotel Ways, which was created by Tetsuya from Tokai On Air!
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
I've been wanting to come here for a long time.
This place is very popular even in Yuriyaku!
They are going to show us the rooms that started in May today.
Let's go right away!
Please do.
Let's go!
Let's go inside!
Be careful.
Let's go inside.
Ready?
Whoa!
Ta-da!
Oh, my gosh! Can you see them? The sign, and this?
Look, a map? Amazing!
Mr. Oyaizu is showing us everything.
He's searching from the first floor. He's searching, Oyaizu-kun.
I see. Cute.
This way! This way!
I get excited just entering.
The sign's so big. And the sign is huge.
Good!
Glad to hear it.
I'm looking forward to it. Today we're going to show you a lot of the rooms.
Let's go! It looks like it's at the end of the street, so let's go!
Wow!
A little orange. I see an orange door.
Here's Mr. Oyaizu, too.
He's so cute!
This is the door, isn't it?
Wow!
The door from Mr. Tetsuya in orange.
I'd like to enter this room first.
Here we go! Ready?
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Stylish.
The door was orange, so I wondered what it would look like.
It's so nice!
Amazing!
It's so Japanese!
There's a notebook, too.
It's true!
This is the rumored Kote Oyasama Notebook!
Notebook
The Notebook for Parents of Small Hands
Wow!
I didn't know it was here.
I'm so glad
It's a notebook that all the guests
This is the notebook that all the guests write in. This is the notebook that everyone writes in.
Why don't we write in our own notebooks?
Me?
Am I good?
I think you write nice things.
Well then...
Okay, bye.
Yes, I wrote it.
Your parents are the best!
I will definitely stay there again!
I love you so much!
Merry duo!
I love it!
It's kind of stylish.
The mirror.
It's so stylish.
I want to be in the mirror with everyone.
Do you want to take a picture?
Here you go.
I want to take a picture with only a half-body station.
The ring light.
That's a light, right?
Oh, wow.
I like this one.
This one's good, right?
Okay, here we go.
There, there, there, there.
Okay, let's all take a look at this, because it looks like it's got a little bit of Americana in it.
I want to see it.
Stylish!
Oh, wow!
Fireworks again!
Wait, isn't there a lot of Americorps?
I mean, it's like, you know, you're living in a house and everything.
I mean, there's even a design for that.
Normal?
It's just... it's kind of a waste.It's just... it's such a waste.
I have a regular one, so I can use it.
Oh, my God.
There's so many different kinds.
There's so many.
I want one.
I want one of these.
Okay, we've arrived at the next room.
Yay!
Here's Oyaizu again.
He's looking for you.
Where is he?
I'd like to see what kind of room it is now.
I'm sure you will.
Let's go in!
Yay! We're going in!
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's open it up!
Jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan!
You're right...
It's true.
No, it's not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
It's a room for the Yao-Yao-Dan.
Sorry to bother you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm connected to your stomach.
So, this is Yogitan.
This is Yoyo-dan's room.
It's so spacious!
So spacious!
This is Yogi's room.
It's a big room, but it's a little bigger than the other rooms.
This one is like this.
Wow!
There's enough water and toiletries for two people!
This is a room for everyone! A room for everyone.
I wish we could all come.
We can all stay here.
I don't know if you can tell... what this room looks like.
Oh, wow.
It's so deep.
It's got a great depth to it.
Wow, that's great news!
Yay!
Everyone should go to different places
It's so spacious!
We can all stay together.
Now let's go on and on and on and on and on to the next room!
Room number three.
Orange!
That's right!
Orange.
All orange!
The next room is here!
Ta-da!
Earlier, the door was all orange, but this time...
But this time, it's a colorful room called “Live Green”.
Live Green
Live green.
I've got a Laimu.
Yes, yes, yes.
But it's definitely not lime.
It's green, and it's dark, and it's dark, and it's live.
It's a darker color, and it's live.
Okay, let's get started.
Ready?
Ta-da!
Wow!
Amazing!
Green.
Not green. It's not green.
Are we going in?
Let's go in.
Okay, I'll mix it up.
I think I'll go for it.
It's green everywhere you look.
It's green.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Ta-da!
Oh, my God.
That's great.
What's that?
Huh?
But they're dots.
Dots.
Oh, wow.
Let's see.
Let's see...
Can I show you something?
I don't see anything.
I don't know. Dot.
Oh, great.
I want to stare at it for a second.
Okay, well...
Which way are you looking?
Oh, this way.
What? What's what?
What?
What's what?
It's a face.
What?
You're not even in a relationship here.
Faces.
Faces. Your face.
Hmm?
Look.
What?
Oh, my.
Yes, it's true.
Is this it?
Here?
Right here.
Here!
Right here!
That's it! Get in close!
Right here, right?
What?
Here?
It's on the screen.
If you look closer, you can see the dots.
It's just dots. It's fashionable.
I don't know why they don't put them there.
It's getting farther and farther away.
Dendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendend.
I'm staring at it
I can't tell if it's not a screen
I want you to see the screen
I'm in sixth place, Aimidokun?
I feel like when I stare at them, they're like...
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? I thought.
That's great.
He's staring at her.
Oh, he's so cute.
It's amazing, really.
Okay, so now we're on the fourth floor.
Oh, my God, you're getting a tan.
Rooftop?
The top floor. The top floor.
It's a completely different atmosphere when you're on the top floor.
The view is so different.
It's a beautiful day.
And the next room is this one.
Orange door.
What's this room?
This is the intangible room that you don't often see on Mr. Gachatia's personal channel.
That's great.
You put it in the video, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm so glad. It looks like we can go there.
You can actually see it.
Oh my God.
Premium.
Well, I'll be there as soon as I can.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
It's huge!
What's it like?
Wow, it's kind of, you know, chic.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Oh, it's big.
It's big.
Excuse me.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I get a good look at that.
That's what I'm looking at.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, are you sure?
Are you sure?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous. I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
She's so cute.
Oh, my God.
This couch, this couch is the first time I've seen it in person.
Oh, wow.
It's like the color changes depending on the angle you look at it.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
I'm changing over here.
I'm comfortable.
It's the same
Card planning
Decide the card
Oh, Seattle again!
Here are the goods from Hotel Oyasuru!
Amazing!
So cute!
Let's take a look at them one by one.
First, the pearls.
May I?
Oh, my God.
It's in there.
It's so fluffy.
But I don't know if I can use it.
I know.
Porch.
Pouch? Pouch, then.
It's cute.
This is a pouch.
Very nice.
All embroidered. It's all embroidery.
It's got a town on it.
Thank you.
Isn't that what a lash is?
When you put it in your makeup?
And it's so spread out.
You can put anything in there, right?
It can hold a lot.
It's so cute.
We use a lot of pouches.
That's why I want one.
It's so cute!
Here's the tote bag.
The tote bag is also big!
This one is also a tote bag
It's got a side pocket.
There's a lot of room in this one, too.
Oh, wow!
It's amazing.
Can you feel it?
It's a lot of space.
It holds a lot.
About 100 minutes.
It's so cute!
This is Lumia.
I want this so bad.
Oh, my God.
I want it.
Wait a minute.
It's really comfortable to the touch.
It's so cute!
I like this one.
And here are the pants.
Ta-da!
So good! Very nice.
You can wear it like this.
You can wear it like this
The material is so good.
It's really good.
And it's stretchy.
It stretches a little bit.
It's super easy to wear.
I haven't worn it yet, but it's definitely easy to wear.
Stress-free, right?
I know, right?
Sleep well in this.
I haven't been sleeping well lately, so I want to wear this and get a good night's sleep.
It's a size small.
It's roomy.
Yes.
I've been wanting to buy one.
I can walk around in this.
There's so many of them.
Not at all.
I'll stand out like a bat out of hell.
I'll totally stand out.
It's cute.
It's nice.
Coffee.
It's cute.
Wait a minute, the picture is cute.
Cute.
What's this?
It's a collaboration with R Stand Coffee.
Amazing!
R Coffee Stand
This coffee is R Stand Coffee Stand
R Coffee Stand Mr. R Coffee Stand
R Coffee Stand
Sorry.
This dripsto coffee looks like a collaboration with R Coffee Stand!
That's what the awesome illustration looks like.
Right here in the store.
That's awesome!
Here's Koeizukun drinking it.
So cute!
I can't drink this either.
You can't open it.
It's nice.
Hey...
That's amazing.
That's cheap.
Let's start with marshmallows.
Yes, ma'am.
And finally, water.
I'd like to have some.
What is it?
Something from Tetsuya?
Yes, I do.
Yes.
Orange. Do you have a bottle of orange mother?
Hmm?
Ah! Yes! Sorry!
We don't have orange nectar!
I'm sorry.
We don't have any orange rinds!
Excuse me!
I'm sorry.
We do not have any orange rinds!
What?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Thank you very much! Thank you!
Surprise!
Thank you for your hard work
Good afternoon, sir.
Thanks for your time.
Just a minute.
Good work, sir.
I'm sweating
Thank you for your help
Just a moment, please
Please wait a moment
Sweat.
Sweat
You're tired, sir.
Thank you for your hard work
Good work, sir.
How long have you been here?
About two hours
About 2 hours
Thank you for watching
Ending
Since it seems you've come this far.
I would like to fulfill my role as president.
I will do my best.
I'm more nervous than I've ever been in my life.
Let's keep going.
- Fluffy.
- Fluffy. - Embroidery.
- That's great. - That's great.
Feels so good on the skin.
- Oh, this is it. - Yeah, it is.
That's amazing. And it's like...
I want one of these in print. I want one so bad.
- I want it. - Yeah. - I'd like that. - Yeah.
- Really. - One more time.
- This is the top one. - The top one?
- Wow. - Wow.
- I want it.
This is the coffee, right?
Earl's Stand Coffee.
Earl.
Earl?
Coffee
coffee
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I can spare you a couple of weeks.
Thank you very much.
- Pump? - A tee shirt...
- 20 yen.
- What? - Oh!
- Handmade tee shirts.
Handmade tee shirts
- That's great. - That's great.
- Thank you.
And sunglasses.
- Great. - Great.
Oh, I can't do without them.
I'd wear them, too.
I'm so nervous.
I can't stand up.
I can't feel parallel.
I'm shaking.
I'm kind of in need of a wall right now.
- I'm fine with a wall. - I'm glad.
- Great. - Great.
- Excellent. - Excellent.
Excellent. - Excellent. Thank you very much.
- I'm with Utsuya here. - I'm here with Utsuya-san.
- We'll be filming.
What? - How do you want me to do it?
What should I do?
- I can't do anything. - I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Just go back to where you were.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me. - Excuse me.
Excuse me.
- Great. - Embarrassing.
- Embarrassing. - Embarrassing.
Oh, my God, it's really back to year one.
- I'm so glad. - Yes, I mean...
- Tetsuya's here. - No, thanks for coming.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you very much.
- Thank you very much.
It's really a dream to be here with Tetsuya.
- It's too much of a dream. - No, it's all the other way around.
- No, let's see. - It's all backwards.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you very much.
- Thank you. - I'm so happy.
I'm already a little nervous.
I'm a little bit nervous, but we can make water, so let me introduce you to water.
Please, by all means, give it to him.
I'll put it down for you at random when we stop.
If it's a room for two, you get two. If it's a room for four, you get four.
- Wow. - Wow.
It's all very nice, but here's a gimmick.
This is the Sunset City Runner.
- I think it's like - drive
- Sunset city on the drive. - Sunset city on the drive.
I was so nervous, I didn't remember either.
It's so cute.
- Cute. - Cute - Cute
- It's running a little bit. - Looks like it's running.
There's a background in the back.
If you do it like this, it looks like a car is running.
- That's great. - That's great.
- You see it? - Do you see it? Do you see it?
Do you see it? What do you think?
We'll be right there.
Ready?
He's running.
- So cute!
- Cute. - Cute.
Cute. - That's great.
I want them all.
That's great.
It'll be fun to collect them all.
- I want to decorate it. - It's random.
It's random, so it's fun to see which one comes first.
- It's nice. - It's nice.
- So cute. - It's so cute!
Thank you so much.
- That's great. - That's so cute.
You were talking so much.
I was gonna say something, but then I was gonna say...
Surprise!
After this, Tetsuya...
The Tetsuya room.
- Oh?
He said he'll show us around.
- Sure. - Are you sure?
- Is that okay? - Yes, please.
That's great.
I'm a fan of Tetsuya's. Is that okay?
I'm looking forward to it.
I wanted to go.
- What? - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Please. - Please.
Yes, so this angle of view...
I know it's too extravagant a reward.
I'd like to go to the last room.
- Please, please, please, please. - Thank you very much.
- It's right over there.
Yes.
- This way, please. - This way.
- This way. - Oh, great.
You know...
I'd like you to come in here right away.
Close your eyes.
I'd like you to come inside.
And open your eyes at the same time?
- Oh, okay.
Okay. - Okay.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
- Guys, two. - Let's go.
Let's go. Oh, sure.
- We're on a train now? - Yes, it is. - It's running smoothly.
- It's a train now. - To be smoothed out, есть
Well, please come to the sound of the voice.
- Yes, sir.
This way, this way.
I'm this way, box.
- This way, this way, this way.
- Go for that reaction. - Yes.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on. - I'm going.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on. - Here we go.
- yes, wait, there's a lot in there. - this way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
- Five this way. - Five this way.
Come on, come on.
- That's pretty far. - He's pushing the camera.
He's pushing the camera.
Here we go.
Ready? Seino
Open your eyes, please.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Here's a hint.
I took it down just for this room.
This is my wall of decision.
You'll have to forgive me for watching.
The real teacher says it's here, too.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
It's like a little guessing room.
Oh, my God!
What am I to be seen by my guessers?
What is this?
Oh, my God, it's real.
It's too cool!
I'm a little bit like a prince.
And the school uniform...
Youth...
School uniform...
Oh, really!
That's amazing!
Look!
So cute!
That's me when I was little.
Oh, my gosh!
This is it.
If you take a picture of me on this side of the panel
it looks like I'm holding him like this.
Aichan, you've made it!
Are you sure you want to go first?
Excuse me.
He's so cute!
She's amazing!
Are you coming? This way.
Oh! Ooh!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God.
No more food.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
I can't even get a drink.
I'll just try to take a picture of this hand.
I'm trying to make it look like a trey.
That's great!
entrevist is good!
Grin.
Hey, can I get a little something around here?
Oh, yeah!
Asa Inaza, Grandma.
Okay, bye.
Possibilit.
I'm so happy.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Yo, moved
Good night.
Don't like it today.
Oh, wow.
There's a lot more to this room.
What's going on?
I'll show you a picture.
I felt something.
Here.
You're feeling it, aren't you?
I think I'm going to sleep in a bed in the hotel.
You can sleep with me.
Oh, my God!
That's amazing!
You look nervous. You look nervous.
I can't sleep.
I can't wake up in the morning and go back to sleep.
I'm really just... I'm just the president of the hotel.
You know what?
I'm going to state the obvious, but would you like to sleep with me?
Ai-chan, Ai-chan I'm coming.
Sleep... sleep... sleep...
Sleep standing up.
If I take a picture of you while you sleep...
I can take a picture of you with your arms around me.
That's great! That's amazing!
I'm starting to feel like I'm not living up to my potential.
Are you okay? It's like...
I was wondering if I could try it for a minute.
Debutantes?
Excuse me.
Oh, my God! I'm so nervous!
Really?
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm freezing.
This is one thing, but there's something else, too, if you'd like.
Can I ask you to come over here?
Excuse me.
By the way, we have two beds.
You have a bed.
It's a little different.
This one is slightly different.
He's already stopped.
He was very kind.
That's great.
A lot came out.
It's too luxurious.
Amazing.
It's good.
It's interesting.
One last thing...I'm going to open the door for you, because it looks like there's something wonderful in there.
Ready. Seino.
Welcome.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Amazing.
Welcome.
I'm here, and if you take a picture of me, you can take a picture of me from behind while I'm brushing my teeth.
It's as if we are together.
Yes, I'll try to put it right.
Good morning.
That's great.
I want you to enjoy your stay in the morning and after waking up, and last but not least, I want you to stay overnight in the room.
Yes.
And lastly, I was wondering if you would be using this room as well,
Can one of you please open the door?
So you're going to open it?
Yes.
Please go ahead.
I'll go on.
One more time.
It's an old monk's room, but I made it to today's lid specs.
It's definitely a little different than usual. I'm crying.
Nose plugs and tears. The Morisaka-san stage.
You can enjoy it all the time.
It's a great room!
Thank you very much!
So I had the opportunity to tour the room with Tetsuya!
I was so happy that I don't remember the second half of the tour, it was like a dream!
I was so happy in this really nice hotel!
Thank you so much!
I feel exactly the same way.
There is something I want to say to all of you.
The first time I saw Ms. Miyaji was at the Fujikyu in 2023. The first time I saw Ms. Miyajyo was at the Fujikyu in 2023.
Yes, thank you.
I saw this room then, too.
I was thinking that the hotel project had started and I wanted something like a cleaning service as a president.
I thought I wanted something like cleaning as a president and I was kind of happy.
But then I saw your rooms and I thought that there were not so many happy people here.
I was so glad to see you all here and I was able to use you as a reference.
And I asked Shinobu to make it for me, and the Stylish Company made it.
I was so inspired by you all!
I mean, it's really cool, but...
It's great!
Thank you very much.
So, thanks to all of you, your inspiration has already had such an impact on the hotel.
And it's thanks to all of you that we've been able to create these outfits.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
We were wearing them, weren't we?
I'll show you a picture of all of us.
Oh, well, thank you.
That was the birth story.
Thank you very much.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
So today we are going to stay here in Wakazaki.
I'm going to spend the day in Okazaki!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much!
And what's more, tomorrow's schedule!
Tetsuya-san has planned it for me!
I made a little plan!
Thank you very much!
Even if you're a newcomer, you can get a feel of Tokai On Air.
I've chosen a place that's not too scary.
Please enjoy!
Thank you very much! Thank you!
I'm going to enjoy it!
I'm sure you'll have a great time!
I'm looking forward to it!
I will enjoy Okazaki a lot and to the fullest!
Now, I hope you enjoyed this video.
I hope you enjoyed this video.
Please subscribe to our channel, click the “Good” button, and leave a comment!
Thank you!
That's all for now, Niyari Equal Joy and
This is Tetsuya from Tokai On Air!
Thank you very much!